thedailypolls.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy & Cookies | The Daily Polls

Cookies help us deliver our services. By using our services, you agree to our use of cookies.This website is using cookies

Got it

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  1. Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  2. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  3. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  4. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  5. Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  6. We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  7. We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**Cookies Policy**

THEDAILYPOLLS.COM values your privacy and does not share personal information with 3rd parties nor do we store any information about your visit to this website other than to analyze and optimize your content and reading experience through the use of cookies.

**You can[opt to turn off the use of cookies](http://www.wikihow.com/Disable-Cookies) at anytime by changing settings in your web browser.**

Examples of data collected from visitors to this site include:

1\. Google Analytics is used analyze traffic. This service is used to collect information such as the following from visitors:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * visitor location (town/state/country)
  * Type of web browser
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks on links

No personally identifiable information is collected by these services (i.e., no names or other personal information).

2\. THEDAILYPOLLS.COM uses several services to serve advertisements. These services may use cookies to help them tailor ads to individual user interests. We have no access to or control over these cookies as they are served by a third party.

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and was last updated on December 24, 2015.

Contact: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
